<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.mindswap.pellet"
      label="Pellet OWL reasoner"
      version="1.5.0.1"
      provider-name="Mindswap.org"
      image="jimsLogo.gif">

   <description url="about.html">
      Pellet is an open-source Java based OWL DL reasoner. It can be used in conjunction with 
either Jena or OWL-API libraries. Pellet provides functionalities to validate ontology 
species, check consistency of ontologies, classify the taxonomy, check entailments and 
answer a subset of RDQL queries (known as ABox queries in DL terminology).
   </description>

   <copyright url="about.html">
      Copyright (c) 2003 Ron Alford, Mike Grove, Bijan Parsia, Evren Sirin

This product includes following software components:
* Jena toolkit (http://jena.sourceforge.net) developed by HP Labs
* OWLAPI library (http://sourceforge.net/projects/owlapi) developed by WonderWeb project
* ATerm library (http://www.cwi.nl/htbin/sen1/twiki/bin/view/SEN1/ATermLibrary) developed by CWI, LORIA-INRIA
   </copyright>

   <license url="about.html">
      Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the &quot;Software&quot;), to
deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the
rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or
sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS
IN THE SOFTWARE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="PlatformKit update site" url="http://ssel.vub.ac.be/platformkit/update"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="com.hp.hpl.jena"/>
      <import plugin="org.junit"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.mindswap.pellet"
         download-size="1620"
         install-size="2056"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.semanticweb.owl"
         download-size="2780"
         install-size="2780"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.semanticweb.owl.doc"
         download-size="5468"
         install-size="5468"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
