<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="be.ac.vub.platformkit.kb.jena"
      label="PlatformKit Jena Adapter"
      version="1.2.0"
      provider-name="Vrije Universiteit Brussel">

   <description>
      PlatformKit adapter for the Jena framework.

Jena is a Java framework for building Semantic Web applications. It provides a programmatic environment for RDF, RDFS and OWL, including a rule-based inference engine.

Jena is open source and grown out of work with the HP Labs Semantic Web Programme.

The Jena Framework includes:

    * A RDF API
    * Reading and writing RDF in RDF/XML, N3 and N-Triples
    * An OWL API
    * In-memory and persistent storage
    * RDQL – a query language for RDF
   </description>

   <copyright>
      © Copyright 2005, 2006, 2007, 2008 Dennis Wagelaar, Vrije Universiteit
Brussel

* Jena (http://jena.sourceforge.net/) *

© Copyright 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005 2006, 2007 Hewlett-Packard Development Company, LP

Jena includes software developed by the Apache Software Foundation (http://www.apache.org/).
Jena is built on top of other sub-systems which we gratefully acknowledge:
* Xerces
* JUnit
* Jakarta ORO
* ICU4J
* util.concurrent from Doug Lea
   </copyright>

   <license>
      Vrije Universiteit Brussel makes available all content in this
plug-in. The Content in this plug-in is provided to you under
the terms and conditions of the Eclipse Public License Version
1.0 (&quot;EPL&quot;). A copy of the EPL is available at http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html.

Applicable Licenses

PlatformKit is built upon a number of other open source technologies and products. Here is a list of those products with their licenses.

* Jena (http://jena.sourceforge.net/) *

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
3. The name of the author may not be used to endorse or promote
products derived from this software without specific prior written
permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE
GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE
OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

* ICU4J *

ICU 1.8.1 and later COPYRIGHT AND PERMISSION NOTICE Copyright
(c) 1995-2003 International Business Machines Corporation and others All
rights reserved. Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any
person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files
(the &quot;Software&quot;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including
without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,
distribute, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to
whom the Software is furnished to do so, provided that the above copyright
notice(s) and this permission notice appear in all copies of the Software
and that both the above copyright notice(s) and this permission notice
appear in supporting documentation.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY
RIGHTS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR HOLDERS INCLUDED IN THIS
NOTICE BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, OR ANY SPECIAL INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES, OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR
PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS
ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS
SOFTWARE. Except as contained in this notice, the name of a copyright
holder shall not be used in advertising or otherwise to promote the sale,
use or other dealings in this Software without prior written authorization
of the copyright holder.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="SOFT update site" url="http://soft.vub.ac.be/eclipse/update-3.5"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="be.ac.vub.platformkit"/>
      <import plugin="org.junit"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="be.ac.vub.platformkit.kb.jena"
         download-size="36"
         install-size="36"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="be.ac.vub.platformkit.kb.jena.doc"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
