<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="be.ac.vub.platformkit.kb.owlapi"
      label="PlatformKit OWLAPI Adapter"
      version="1.0.2"
      provider-name="Vrije Universiteit Brussel">

   <description>
      PlatformKit adapter for the OWLAPI framework.

The OWL API is a Java interface and implementation for the W3C
Web Ontology Language OWL. The latest version of the API is focused
towards OWL 2 which encompasses, OWL-Lite, OWL-DL and some elements
of OWL-Full.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      © Copyright 2005, 2006, 2007, 2008 Dennis Wagelaar, Vrije Universiteit
Brussel.

* OWLAPI (http://sourceforge.net/projects/owlapi) *

© Copyright 2006, 2007, University of Manchester.
© Copyright 2007, Clark &amp; Parsia.
© Copyright 2007, Ulm University.

* Pellet (http://www.mindswap.org/2003/pellet/) *

© Copyright 2003 Ron Alford, Mike Grove, Bijan Parsia, Evren Sirin.

* ATerm (http://www.cwi.nl/htbin/sen1/twiki/bin/view/SEN1/ATermLibrary) *

© Copyright 2002-2007, CWI and INRIA.
All rights reserved.

* RELAX NG *

© Copyright (c) 2001, Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd, Sun Microsystems.
All rights reserved.

* SUN XML DATATYPES LIBRARY (xsdlib) *

© Copyright 2001-2006 Sun Microsystems, Inc. 901 San Antonio Road, Palo Alto,
California, 94303, U.S.A. All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      Vrije Universiteit Brussel makes available all content in this
plug-in. The Content in this plug-in is provided to you under
the terms and conditions of the Eclipse Public License Version
1.0 (&quot;EPL&quot;). A copy of the EPL is available at http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html.

Applicable Licenses

PlatformKit is built upon a number of other open source technologies and products. Here is a list of those products with their licenses.

* OWLAPI (http://sourceforge.net/projects/owlapi) *

Modifications to the initial code base are copyright of their
respective authors, or their employers as appropriate.  Authorship
of the modifications may be determined from the ChangeLog placed
at the end of this file.

This library is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
modify it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public
License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
version 2.1 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

This library is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public
License along with this library; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA  02110-1301
USA

* Pellet (http://www.mindswap.org/2003/pellet/) *

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &quot;Software&quot;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.

* ATerm (http://www.cwi.nl/htbin/sen1/twiki/bin/view/SEN1/ATermLibrary) *

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
  notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
* Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
  notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
  documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
* Neither the name of the University of California, Berkeley nor the
  names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products
  derived from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE REGENTS AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE REGENTS AND CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND
ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

* RELAX NG *

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:

    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
    notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
    the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
    distribution.

    Neither the names of the copyright holders nor the names of its
    contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived
    from this software without specific prior written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE REGENTS OR
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,
EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR
PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

* SUN XML DATATYPES LIBRARY (xsdlib) *

Redistribution and  use in  source and binary  forms, with  or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:

- Redistributions  of  source code  must  retain  the above  copyright
  notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

- Redistribution  in binary  form must  reproduct the  above copyright
  notice, this list of conditions  and the following disclaimer in the
  documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.

Neither  the  name   of  Sun  Microsystems,  Inc.  or   the  names  of
contributors may be  used to endorse or promote  products derived from
this software without specific prior written permission.

This software is provided &quot;AS IS,&quot; without a warranty of any kind. ALL
EXPRESS  OR   IMPLIED  CONDITIONS,  REPRESENTATIONS   AND  WARRANTIES,
INCLUDING  ANY  IMPLIED WARRANTY  OF  MERCHANTABILITY,  FITNESS FOR  A
PARTICULAR PURPOSE  OR NON-INFRINGEMENT, ARE HEREBY  EXCLUDED. SUN AND
ITS  LICENSORS SHALL  NOT BE  LIABLE  FOR ANY  DAMAGES OR  LIABILITIES
SUFFERED BY LICENSEE  AS A RESULT OF OR  RELATING TO USE, MODIFICATION
OR DISTRIBUTION OF  THE SOFTWARE OR ITS DERIVATIVES.  IN NO EVENT WILL
SUN OR ITS  LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOST  REVENUE, PROFIT OR DATA,
OR  FOR  DIRECT,   INDIRECT,  SPECIAL,  CONSEQUENTIAL,  INCIDENTAL  OR
PUNITIVE  DAMAGES, HOWEVER  CAUSED  AND REGARDLESS  OF  THE THEORY  OF
LIABILITY, ARISING  OUT OF  THE USE OF  OR INABILITY TO  USE SOFTWARE,
EVEN IF SUN HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

You acknowledge that Software is not designed,licensed or intended for
use  in the  design,  construction, operation  or  maintenance of  any
nuclear facility.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="SOFT update site" url="http://soft.vub.ac.be/eclipse/update-3.5"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="be.ac.vub.platformkit"/>
      <import plugin="org.junit"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.commons.logging"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.xerces"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="be.ac.vub.platformkit.kb.owlapi"
         download-size="32"
         install-size="32"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.semanticweb.owl"
         download-size="2940"
         install-size="2940"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.semanticweb.owl.doc"
         download-size="5636"
         install-size="5636"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.mindswap.pellet"
         download-size="936"
         install-size="936"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="aterm"
         download-size="352"
         install-size="352"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.sun.xsdlib"
         download-size="476"
         install-size="476"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.relaxng"
         download-size="40"
         install-size="40"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
