<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.hp.hpl.jena"
      label="Jena"
      version="2.3.0.1"
      provider-name="Hewlett-Packard Development Company, LP"
      image="jena-logo-small.gif">

   <description url="about.html">
      Jena is a Java framework for building Semantic Web applications. It provides a programmatic environment for RDF, RDFS and OWL, including a rule-based inference engine.

Jena is open source and grown out of work with the HP Labs Semantic Web Programme.

The Jena Framework includes:

    * A RDF API
    * Reading and writing RDF in RDF/XML, N3 and N-Triples
    * An OWL API
    * In-memory and persistent storage
    * RDQL – a query language for RDF
   </description>

   <copyright url="about.html">
      © Copyright 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005 Hewlett-Packard
Development Company, LP

Jena includes software developed by the Apache Software Foundation
(http://www.apache.org/).

Jena is built on top of other sub-systems which we gratefully
acknowledge:
* Xerces
* JUnit
* Jakarta ORO
* ICU4J
* util.concurrent from Doug Lea
   </copyright>

   <license url="about.html">
      Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
3. The name of the author may not be used to endorse or promote
products derived from this software without specific prior written
permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR ``AS IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESS
OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE
GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE
OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="PlatformKit update site" url="http://ssel.vub.ac.be/platformkit/update"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="com.hp.hpl.jena"
         download-size="12080"
         install-size="13168"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="com.hp.hpl.jena.doc"
         download-size="4240"
         install-size="4605"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
